Do you see this?
What's happening here?
That's a hint that the photo finish system at the Olympics isn't actually giving us a photo.
And that's why it looks a little weird.
So these two runners, Kashane Thompson and Noah Lyles, both finished the hundred meter race with an official time of nine point seven nine seconds.
The announcer had called it for Thompson, but it turned out his torso crossed that line five thousandths of a second after Lyles.
How do they know that?
Well, Omega, which is the official timekeeper for the Olympics, has a finish line camera that can capture forty thousand frames per second.
But instead of a normal camera, it scans one vertical slice.
So this photo finish picture isn't capturing a moment in time, it's capturing a place, the finish line, and what each body part of each runner looked like as they were crossing it.
Those vertical slices are then spread out horizontally by their time code so that the operator can mark their chests with a red line.
The ground is white because this camera is only capturing the finish line, and the logos come from a billboard that only the finish line camera can read.